[
        {
       "response": "ن ا ر و ت و",
        "question": "ناروتو"
    },
            {
       "response": "م ا د ا ر ا",
        "question": "مادارا"
    },
            {
       "response": "م ي ن ا ت و",
        "question": "ميناتو"
    },
            {
       "response": "ك ا ك ا ش ي",
        "question": "كاكاشي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا و ب ي ت و",
        "question": "اوبيتو"
    },
            {
       "response": "س ا س و ر ي",
        "question": "ساسوري"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا س و م ا",
        "question": "اسوما"
    },
            {
       "response": "ش ي ك ا م ا ر و",
        "question": "شيكامارو"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا ي ن و",
        "question": "اينو"
    },
            {
       "response": "ت ش و ج ي",
        "question": "تشوجي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ه ي ن ا ت ا",
        "question": "هيناتا"
    },
            {
       "response": "ش ي ن و",
        "question": "شينو"
    },
            {
       "response": "ك ي ب ا",
        "question": "كيبا"
    },
            {
       "response": "غ ا ب ي م ا ر و",
        "question": "غابيمارو"
    },
            {
       "response": "ك ا ن ي ك ي",
        "question": "كانيكي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ت و ك ا",
        "question": "توكا"
    },
            {
       "response": "ك و ر و ك و",
        "question": "كوروكو"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا ي ت ا ت ش ي",
        "question": "ايتاتشي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ل و ف ي",
        "question": "لوفي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ز و ر و",
        "question": "زورو"
    },
            {
       "response": "ش ا ن ك س",
        "question": "شانكس"
    },
            {
       "response": "س ا ن ج ي",
        "question": "سانجي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ج ي ر ا ي ا",
        "question": "جيرايا"
    },
            {
       "response": "ت س و ن ا د ي",
        "question": "تسونادي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا و ر ي ت ش ي م ا ر و",
        "question": "اوريتشيمارو"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا و س و ب",
        "question": "اوسوب"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا ي س",
        "question": "ايس"
    },
            {
       "response": "ي ا ت و",
        "question": "ياتو"
    },
            {
       "response": "ه ي و ر ي",
        "question": "هيوري"
    },
            {
       "response": "ب ي ش ا م و ن",
        "question": "بيشامون"
    },
            {
       "response": "س ي ك ي",
        "question": "سيكي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا ي ر ي ن",
        "question": "ايرين"
    },
            {
       "response": "ل ي ف ا ي",
        "question": "ليفاي"
    },
            {
       "response": "م ي ك ا س ا",
        "question": "ميكاسا"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا ر م ي ن",
        "question": "ارمين"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا ي ر و ي ن",
        "question": "ايروين"
    },
            {
       "response": "ز ي ك",
        "question": "زيك"
    },
            {
       "response": "ت و د و ر و م ك ي",
        "question": "تودوروكي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ن ا ن ا م ي",
        "question": "نانامي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ت و ج ي",
        "question": "توجي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ن و ب ا ر ا",
        "question": "نوبارا"
    },
            {
       "response": "ي و ج ي",
        "question": "يوجي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا ي ت ا د و ر ي",
        "question": "ايتادوري"
    },
            {
       "response": "غ و ج و",
        "question": "غوجو"
    },
            {
       "response": "غ ي ت و",
        "question": "غيتو"
    },
            {
       "response": "م ا ه ي ت و",
        "question": "ماهيتو"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا س ت ا",
        "question": "استا"
    },
            {
       "response": "ي و ن و",
        "question": "يونو"
    },
            {
       "response": "ن و ي ل",
        "question": "نويل"
    },
            {
       "response": "ي ا م ي",
        "question": "يامي"
    },
            {
       "response": "م ي د و ر ي ا",
        "question": "ميدوريا"
    },
            {
       "response": "د ي ك و",
        "question": "ديكو"
    },
            {
       "response": "ك ا ت ش ا ن",
        "question": "كاتشان"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا و ل م ا ي ت",
        "question": "اول مايت"
    },
            {
       "response": "ف ا ن ي ت ا س",
        "question": "فانيتاس"
    },
            {
       "response": "د و م ي ن ي ك",
        "question": "دومينيك"
    },
            {
       "response": "ن و ي",
        "question": "نوي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ل ا ي ت",
        "question": "لايت"
    },
            {
       "response": "ك ي ر ا",
        "question": "كيرا"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا ل",
        "question": "ال"
    },
            {
       "response": "ن ي ر",
        "question": "نير"
    },
            {
       "response": "ن ي ر و",
        "question": "نيرو"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا ش ي ل ا د",
        "question": "اشيلاد"
    },
            {
       "response": "ث و ر ك ي ل",
        "question": "ثوركيل"
    },
            {
       "response": "ث و ر ف ي ن",
        "question": "ثورفين"
    },
            {
       "response": "ث و ر ز",
        "question": "ثورز"
    },
            {
       "response": "ه ا ش ي ر ا م ا",
        "question": "هاشيراما"
    },
            {
       "response": "س ا ر و ت و ب ي",
        "question": "ساروتوبي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ب ا ي ن",
        "question": "باين"
    },
            {
       "response": "د ي د ا ر ا",
        "question": "ديدارا"
    },
            {
       "response": "ه ي د ا ن",
        "question": "هيدان"
    },
            {
       "response": "ك ا ك و ز و",
        "question": "كاكوزو"
    },
            {
       "response": "م ي غ و م ي",
        "question": "ميغومي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ش ي ن ي ت ش ي",
        "question": "شينيتشي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا ي ز و م ي",
        "question": "ايزومي"
    },
            {
       "response": "م ي غ ي",
        "question": "ميغي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ي ا م ا ت و",
        "question": "ياماتو"
    },
            {
       "response": "س ا ي",
        "question": "ساي"
    },
            {
       "response": "س و ر ا",
        "question": "سورا"
    },
            {
       "response": "س ا ك و ر ا",
        "question": "ساكورا"
    },
            {
       "response": "ك و ر ا م ا",
        "question": "كوراما"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا ي ل و م ي",
        "question": "ايلومي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ه ي س و ك ا",
        "question": "هيسوكا"
    },
            {
       "response": "م ي ر و ي م",
        "question": "ميرويم"
    },
            {
       "response": "ك و ر ا ب ي ك ا",
        "question": "كورابيكا"
    },
            {
       "response": "ك ي ل و ا",
        "question": "كيلوا"
    },
            {
       "response": "غ و ن",
        "question": "غون"
    },
            {
       "response": "غ و ك و",
        "question": "غوكو"
    },
            {
       "response": "غ و ه ا ن",
        "question": "غوهان"
    },
            {
       "response": "ف ي ج ي ت ا",
        "question": "فيجيتا"
    },
            {
       "response": "ب و ل م ا",
        "question": "بولما"
    },
            {
       "response": "ت ر ا ن ك س",
        "question": "ترانكس"
    },
            {
       "response": "ب ي ر و س",
        "question": "بيروس"
    },
            {
       "response": "ز ي ن و",
        "question": "زينو"
    },
            {
       "response": "س ا ي ا ن",
        "question": "سايان"
    },
            {
       "response": "د ر ا غ و ن",
        "question": "دراغون"
    },
             {
       "response": "ا ك ا ن ي",
        "question": "اكاني"
    },
            {
       "response": "ا ك ا م ي",
        "question": "اكامي"
    },
            {
       "response": "ك ا ي ت و",
        "question": "كايتو"
    },
    {
       "response": "س ا س ك ي",
       "question": "ساسكي"
}
      ]